idcgames.com 2019-05-18

# IDC/Games – All your online games for free - MMORPG, MOBA, RTS

## PRIVACY POLICY

_(version 3.2, 15-12-2017)_

This document describes the Privacy Policy of IDC / Games in relation to the data collected by its web pages and applications for mobile devices, reflecting our commitment to maintain and guarantee secure commercial relationships by protecting personal data and guaranteeing the right to the privacy of each of the users of our services.

Any information provided while visiting our website will be treated in accordance with applicable data protection laws and will only be collected, processed and used for lawful and legitimate purposes of which we inform below.

  1. **Stored data and its purpose**

Firstly, in order to monitor and prevent unauthorized uses or activities that may be illegal (eg, to maintain and guarantee security in case of attacks to our computer systems), we store technical information, of an anonymous nature, on the equipment from those who access our hosting servers, such as your IP address.

Additionally, through the installation on your computer or mobile device of a type of programs commonly known as "cookies", we collect anonymous information about your browsing history, necessary for our website and application to be properly displayed on your computer or device. This information, which does not include personal data, will be stored and used privately, for the development of analytics and statistics and improve our website and application, as well as to adapt our offers to your preferences. You may refuse to provide us with such information by preventing the installation of "cookies" through the configuration options of your browser, but certain services may not work properly if you do so. Please, consult the instructions and manuals of your browser for further information.

On the other hand, in order to provide you with the services available through our website and mobile applications, you must first register as a user, during which time we will request a valid email address, and eventually your address and tax identification number (for billing purposes) in case of purchases). This address, in the case of including your real name, is considered personal data, and together with the rest of the requested data will be stored in our user file, duly registered with the Spanish Agency for Data Protection, being necessary that we communicate any update or change that occurs in them.

Finally, the ordinary use of our online video game platform or our mobile applications generates a significant volume of technical data (games, duration, rankings, etc.), which must be stored to guarantee your progress as a player. This information is hosted on our servers, and may be shared with third party developers, but does not include identifying data.

  2. **DATA REPORTING**

The email address used to register as a user may be communicated to the rest of the entities that make up the group to which IDC / Games belongs, in order to be able to offer you information about other of our products and services.

  3. **Consent to receiving commercial communications**

In relation to the above, acceptance of this Privacy Policy during the registration process as a user implies the provision of your consent for the receipt of such information, in the form of newsletters or other commercial communications.

  4. **Third-party networks**

Users can enable access to the web and / or mobile applications of IDC / Games through their account in different social networks, such as Facebook, Twitter, Google+ or YouTube. By enabling this access, they authorize these social networks to communicate certain data included in their profile, such as the user's full name, photos, contact information, personal circumstances, etc.

In the same way, by enabling this access, users expressly authorize us to:

1) access and retain access credentials to those networks;

2) access and preserve the information that these networks communicate to us;

3) publish certain user activity in IDC / Games, such as the user's ranking, in those networks.

On the other hand, certain video games from the IDC / Games catalog are available on third-party platforms, such as Apple Store, Google Play Store or Steam. By registering as a user in these platforms you accept their respective terms of use and privacy policies, but by downloading one of our products you also accept the Privacy Policy of IDC / Games, which will be applied to the data that these platforms communicate about you.

  5. **Right to access, rectify, cancel and oppose (ARCO rights)**

Owners of personal data have the rights of access, rectification, cancellation and opposition. The fastest and easiest way to exercise those rights is by accessing your user account and change your data directly or delete your account. Any information we need to store, under a legal or contractual obligation will be blocked and only used for these purposes instead of being deleted.

To exercise these rights you can write to IDC / Games (by email to [info@idcgames.com](mailto:info@idcgames.com), or by postal address to C/ Pasamar nº 1, local 3, Las Rozas de Madrid, 28231), attaching a copy of some official identification document.

Through the same channels you can also revoke your consent to the use of your contact data for advertising purposes, market research or development of satisfaction surveys at any time, without retroactive effect.

  6. **LEGAL BASIS**

In accordance with the General Data Protection Regulations, users are informed that the legal basis on which the processing of personal data described in this Privacy Policy is based is, principally, the full execution of the contract of the provision of services perfected upon the acceptance of the terms of use of the IDC / Games web or applications, and on a secondary basis, the users' own consent.

If a user refuses to supply the data requested by IDC / Games or to consent to the described treatments, including those not related to the provision of the contracted services, he or she may be prevented from using the Service.

  7. **Modifications**

The Privacy Policy contained on this page may suffer updates, due to changes in legal requirements or improvements and changes on the way we offer and deliver our products and services. These changes will be duly announced in the portal of the website and / or mobile application, and will be effective with the user's subsequent access to them. Notwithstanding the foregoing, we recommend that you visit this page periodically to be able to consult the applicable terms at any given time.
